http://www.enconsafety.com/en/privacy-policy

Last updated: 03/10/2017
Encon Safety Products, Inc. ("us", "we", or "our") operates http://www.enconsafety.com (the "Site"). This page informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use and disclosure of Personal Information we receive from users of the Site.
We use your Personal Information only for providing and improving the Site. By using the Site, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy.
Information Collection And UseWhile using our Site, we may ask you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify you. Personally identifiable information may include, but is not limited to your name ("Personal Information").
Log DataSimilar to many websites, Encon works with service providers to enhance and improve our websites, products, and services. These providers supply tools for traffic monitoring, interest-based advertising, surveys, social media advertising, and email marketing.
We monitor site traffic and technical performance to administer our website, to improve our visitors’ experiences, for research and development of new products and services, evaluate site usage, provide site security, and provide localized content based on geographic location. We collect device identifiers, such as IP address, for this purpose.
For privacy-related information related to Google Analytics or to opt-out, please see: https://support.google.com/analytics/answer/6004245.
CommunicationsWe may use your Personal Information to contact you with newsletters, marketing or promotional materials and other information that uses web beacons to collect data about what content you viewed in an email. If you would like to opt-out of our marketing emails, you may do so from each commercial email we send.
CookiesCookies are files with small amount of data, which may include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a web site and stored on your computer's hard drive.
Like many sites, we use "cookies" to collect information. You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, if you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of our Site.
SecurityThe security of your Personal Information is important to us, but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.
Changes To This Privacy PolicyThis Privacy Policy is effective as of March 10, 2017 and will remain in effect except with respect to any changes in its provisions in the future, which will be in effect immediately after being posted on this page.
We reserve the right to update or change our Privacy Policy at any time and you should check this Privacy Policy periodically. Your continued use of the Service after we post any modifications to the Privacy Policy on this page will constitute your acknowledgment of the modifications and your consent to abide and be bound by the modified Privacy Policy.
If we make any material changes to this Privacy Policy, we will notify you either through the email address you have provided us, or by placing a prominent notice on our website.
Contact UsIf you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the personal information you share with us, please contact us using the contact information below.
Email: This email address is being protected from spambots. You need JavaScript enabled to view it.
Phone: +1 (713) 466-1449
Toll-free in the U.S.: (800) 283-6266
Company Info
6825 W Sam Houston Pkwy. N
Houston, TX 77041
1-800-283-6266 (toll free)
713-466-1449 (direct)
713-466-1703 (fax)
Email Encon
Products
Showers & EyewashPersonal ProtectionWall Storage SolutionsParts & AccessoriesResources
About
Our CompanyConsultationDeliveryEngineeringServicesStandard Compliance
Information
Latest Encon NewsEncon Videos
Product Literature
Legal
Privacy PolicyRegulationsTrademarksTerms & ConditionsSitemap
Social
Facebook
Twitter
Youtube
6825 W Sam Houston Pkwy. N
Houston, TX 77041
1-800-283-6266 (toll free)
713-466-1449 (direct)
713-466-1703 (fax)
Email Encon
ProductsShowers & EyewashCombination ShowersShowersFace & EyewashSelf-Contained PortablesTempered Water SystemsFreeze Protected SystemsWater Blending SolutionsParts & AccessoriesPersonal ProtectionSafety EyewearProtective GogglesHearing ProtectionFace ShieldsVeratti Dual Hazard Protective ClothingArc Flash GlovesProtective Vests & Air Distribution SystemsParts & AccessoriesWall Storage SolutionsSCBA Wall CasesESCBA Wall CasesUtility Respiratory Wall CasesFire Extinguisher Wall CasesResources
Product CatalogsBIM-REVITProduct LiteratureSamplesCompanyGeneral Information
Our CompanyConsultationDeliveryEngineeringServicesStandards ComplianceWarrantyProduct Resources
BIM-REVITProduct LiteraturePrivacy PolicyRegulationsTerms & ConditionsTrademarksMediaDiscover
Latest Encon NewsEncon VideosProduct Resources
BIM-REVITProduct LiteraturePrivacy PolicyRegulationsTerms & ConditionsTrademarksContact
